<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fitwise</string>
    <string name="routine">Routine : </string>
    <string name="forgotPassword">Write your email address below, a temporary password will be sent </string>
    <string name="select">Select a Routine...</string>
    <string name="Firstname_empty">The Firstname is required</string>
    <string name="Lastname_empty">The Lastname is required</string>
    <string name="Email_empty">The Email is required</string>
    <string name="password_empty">The password is required</string>
    <string name="Weight_empty">The Weight is required</string>
    <string name="Height_empty">The Height is required</string>
    <string name="Age_empty">The Age is required</string>
    <string name="Checked_error">Check a Routine please!</string>
    <string name="Gender_error">There is an error with the gender</string>
    <string name="Username_empty">The Username is required</string>
    <string name="Authentication_code_incorrect">The Authentication code is incorrect</string>
    <string name="email_format_error">The email field does not match the format of an email address</string>
    <string name="email_or_password_empty">The email address and password are required</string>
    <string name="advice_1">This exercise has to be made with a horizontal bar placed in height.
Seize the bar, The arms as high as shoulders, palms of hands towards the back. Fire at your arms to go back up your body.</string>
    <string name="advice_2">The exercise is made sat on a machine with high pulley with a bar.
        Bust tilted towards the back, the tense arms, to seize the bar. Pull downwards, up to your breast by blowing.</string>
    <string name="advice_3">The exercise is made sat on the low pulley of the machine.
Use a rope of edition or a handle V.Sat on the ground, the oblique bust forwards,
        the tense arms, to seize the handle or the rope of edition.</string>
    <string name="advice_4">Feet are ruled out by the width of shoulders,
        hands were crossed around the straight bar or on a triangle of edition.
        Tilt the bust forward until approximately 45°, by keeping the right back and the bent knees. Go back up the bar
        at the level of the trunk by making it pass between legs. Return slowly to the initial position.</string>
    <string name="advice_5">The exercise makes lengthened on a right bench, with a bar.
The good back with dish on the bench, the feet put on the ground.</string>
    <string name="advice_6">The exercise makes lengthened on an oblique bench, with a bar.
The back stuck well on the bench, the feet put on the ground.</string>
    <string name="advice_7">The exercise makes lengthened on a declined bench, with an angle of 25 ° approximately.
The load is with a bar.</string>
    <string name="advice_8">The exercise makes seated, on a machine. The good back has dish on the file of the machine.
        Arms outspread, place your forearm on supports.Exercise a push by moving closer your to forearm in front of your head.</string>
    <string name="Try_again">That is not the correct machine,scan again please!!!</string>
    <string name="Uncorrect_machine">That is not the correct machine.</string>
    <string name="Scan_again">Scan again please!!!</string>
</resources>
